import { Question } from "../components/MovieQuiz";

export const seinfeldData: Question[] = [
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the coffee shop where the main characters frequently hang out?",
    options: [
      "Monk's Café",
      "Central Perk",
      "Reggie's Diner",
      "Tom's Restaurant",
    ],
    answer: "Monk's Café",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What item of clothing does Jerry often wear that causes problems in the episode 'The Puffy Shirt'?",
    options: [
      "A puffy shirt",
      "A velvet suit",
      "A pirate hat",
      "A leather jacket",
    ],
    answer: "A puffy shirt",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Kramer's first name?",
    options: ["Cosmo", "George", "Newman", "Art"],
    answer: "Cosmo",
  },
  {
    question: "What is George Costanza's biggest fear?",
    options: ["Getting fired", "Clowns", "Commitment", "Flying"],
    answer: "Commitment",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which character is known for the catchphrase, 'No soup for you!'?",
    options: ["The Soup Nazi", "Jerry", "George", "Newman"],
    answer: "The Soup Nazi",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of Elaine's on-and-off boss at the J. Peterman catalog?",
    options: ["J. Peterman", "Mr. Pitt", "Mr. Lippman", "Mr. Kruger"],
    answer: "J. Peterman",
  },
  {
    question: "What holiday does George’s father, Frank Costanza, invent?",
    options: ["Festivus", "Yada Yada Day", "The Human Fund", "Costanza Day"],
    answer: "Festivus",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Jerry’s nemesis who lives in his building?",
    options: ["Newman", "Kramer", "Banya", "Peterman"],
    answer: "Newman",
  },
  {
    question: "What does Elaine famously say is her favorite part of a muffin?",
    options: ["The top", "The bottom", "The wrapper", "The whole thing"],
    answer: "The top",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What does Kramer try to create in his apartment, leading to major problems?",
    options: [
      "A hot tub",
      "A chicken coop",
      "A sushi restaurant",
      "A smoking lounge",
    ],
    answer: "A hot tub",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the movie that Jerry and his friends can never seem to see?",
    options: [
      "Rochelle, Rochelle",
      "Prognosis Negative",
      "Death Blow",
      "CheckMate",
    ],
    answer: "Rochelle, Rochelle",
  },
];
